const quizArr = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the full name of Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)?",
    options: {
      A: "Mohammed Ibn Abdullah, Ibn Abdul Mutalib, Ibn Hashem",
      B: "Muhammad ibn Ali",
      C: "Muhammad ibn Ibrahim",
      D: "Muhammad ibn Hasan",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "In which city was Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) born?",
    options: {
      A: "Medina",
      B: "Mecca",
      C: "Jerusalem",
      D: "Ta'if",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is the name of the cave where Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) received his first revelation?",
    options: {
      A: "Cave of Hira",
      B: "Cave of Thawr",
      C: "Cave of Uhud",
      D: "Cave of Badr",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What was the profession of Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) before he received prophethood?",
    options: {
      A: "Merchant",
      B: "Farmer",
      C: "Blacksmith",
      D: "Carpenter",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What is the name of the Prophet's wife who was the first to accept Islam?",
    options: {
      A: "Aisha",
      B: "Fatimah",
      C: "Khadijah",
      D: "Zainab",
    },
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is the significance of the Hijrah in the life of Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)?",
    options: {
      A: "It marks the beginning of the Islamic calendar.",
      B: "It was the first battle fought by Muslims.",
      C: "It was the first revelation received.",
      D: "It was the Prophet's marriage to Khadijah.",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Which battle is known as the first major battle fought by Muslims?",
    options: {
      A: "Battle of Uhud",
      B: "Battle of Badr",
      C: "Battle of Khandaq",
      D: "Battle of Tabuk",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the name of the treaty that was signed between the Muslims and the Quraysh?",
    options: {
      A: "Treaty of Hudaybiyyah",
      B: "Treaty of Badr",
      C: "Treaty of Khandaq",
      D: "Treaty of Medina",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What is the name of the last sermon delivered by Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)?",
    options: {
      A: "Sermon of Farewell",
      B: "Sermon of Unity",
      C: "Sermon of Guidance",
      D: "Sermon of Faith",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What year did Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) pass away?",
    options: {
      A: "610 CE",
      B: "632 CE",
      C: "622 CE",
      D: "570 CE",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
];

